<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Hoang&#39;s Pipeline</title>
    <link>https://0xhoang.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Hoang&#39;s Pipeline</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Copyright</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 02:01:58 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://0xhoang.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My Return to Tiki: A New Chapter</title>
      <link>https://0xhoang.github.io/2022/02/my-return-to-tiki-a-new-chapter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://0xhoang.github.io/2022/02/my-return-to-tiki-a-new-chapter/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In early 2022, I made the exciting decision to return to Tiki, a company close to my heart. The driving force behind this decision was the exceptional team and the company&amp;rsquo;s inspiring mission.
What I&amp;rsquo;ve Been Up To Upon my return to Tiki, I embarked on several remarkable projects, making a significant impact:
Project: Sandseel - The Exchange Market Platform
Leveraging the open-source Peatio framework Peatio, I worked on developing this platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the World of Incognito Chain</title>
      <link>https://0xhoang.github.io/2020/02/exploring-the-world-of-incognito-chain/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://0xhoang.github.io/2020/02/exploring-the-world-of-incognito-chain/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Joining the dynamic world of Incognito, a blockchain platform, opened up exciting opportunities to delve into the realm of blockchain and privacy-enhancing technologies.
Website: https://incognito.org
My Role and Contributions During my time with Incognito, I was involved in several significant projects:
Project: Incognito Chain - Platform for Privacy Blockchain
Made modest contributions to core Incognito Chain features Project: Blockchain Backend - Microservices for Incognito Wallet
Transformed the architecture from monolithic to microservices, enhancing scalability and modularity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Embarking on a Professional Journey at Tiki</title>
      <link>https://0xhoang.github.io/2016/08/embarking-on-a-professional-journey-at-tiki/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2016 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://0xhoang.github.io/2016/08/embarking-on-a-professional-journey-at-tiki/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Joining the dynamic world of Tiki, a thriving marketplace for eCommerce brands and sellers, marked a significant step in my professional journey.
Website: https://www.tiki.vn
My Role and Contributions During my tenure at Tiki, I had the opportunity to work on various projects. Here are some of the key projects I was involved in:
Project: Talaria - Platform for Order, Inventory, Shipping, Fulfillment, Checkout
Built comprehensive function tests for Talaria, ensuring its reliability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My New Job at Zinio</title>
      <link>https://0xhoang.github.io/2015/12/my-new-job-at-zinio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2015 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://0xhoang.github.io/2015/12/my-new-job-at-zinio/</guid>
      <description>Introduction At Zinio, a digital eMagazines company, I found myself in a dynamic and diverse work environment.
Website: https://www.zinio.com
What I Did One of the key projects I worked on during my time at Zinio was:
Project: Zenit - Digital Magazine Management Platform
I played a significant role in building the API for this platform, leveraging PHP and Symfony. Technology used: Symfony I conducted research on search engines and implemented ElasticSearch to enhance content discovery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My New Job at CCIntegration</title>
      <link>https://0xhoang.github.io/2014/08/my-new-job-at-ccintegration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2014 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://0xhoang.github.io/2014/08/my-new-job-at-ccintegration/</guid>
      <description>Introduction At CCIntegration, a product company, I embarked on a new phase of my career.
Website: https://www.ccintegration.com
What I Did During my time at CCIntegration, my main responsibilities included:
Frontend Development with AngularJS:
I worked on building the frontend of web applications using AngularJS, a popular JavaScript framework. Technology used: AngularJS Message Queues with RabbitMQ:
I gained experience in building and managing basic message queues using RabbitMQ, a robust messaging platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Second Job at Moxs</title>
      <link>https://0xhoang.github.io/2014/02/my-second-job-at-moxs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2014 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://0xhoang.github.io/2014/02/my-second-job-at-moxs/</guid>
      <description>Introduction At Moxs, an eCommerce company, I continued to expand my experience in the field.
What I Did During my time at Moxs, my primary project was:
Shopware Open Source Website (PHP): I was involved in the development of a website using the open-source platform Shopware. This project was built using PHP. Repository: Shopware My work at Moxs allowed me to delve further into eCommerce and open-source technologies, contributing to my growth in the field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting My First Job at Esc.vn</title>
      <link>https://0xhoang.github.io/2011/08/starting-my-first-job-at-esc.vn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2011 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://0xhoang.github.io/2011/08/starting-my-first-job-at-esc.vn/</guid>
      <description>Introduction At Esc Company, I joined a small but dedicated team with the exciting task of developing a website for our client.
Website: https://www.esc.vn
What I did During my time at Esc.vn, I worked on the following projects:
ASP.NET MVC Website:
Developed a website using ASP.NET MVC, jQuery, and Ajax. Utilized SQL Server for database management. Technologies used: jQuery TomatoCart Open Source Website (PHP):
Created a website using the open-source platform TomatoCart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Encouraging College Students to Acquire Computer Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://0xhoang.github.io/2008/08/encouraging-college-students-to-acquire-computer-knowledge/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2008 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://0xhoang.github.io/2008/08/encouraging-college-students-to-acquire-computer-knowledge/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Encouraging college students to embark on a journey of computer knowledge, starting from the fundamentals and expanding their horizons.
Fundamental Skills Elementary Algorithms and Data Structures
Building a foundation in algorithms and data structures. Creating a Monolithic Ecommerce Website
Understanding the fundamentals of web development by building a monolithic e-commerce website. Frontend Development HTML, CSS, and JavaScript Exploring the basics of web development through HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. Backend Development PHP, MySQL, C, C#, Java</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
